// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Database management system is a collection of _____________ and set of data programs to access them.",
    answer: "Interrelated Data",
    options: [
      "Interrelated Programs",
      "Interrelated DataStructures",
      "Interrelated Data",
      "Databases"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which among the following shows only the user interface to the user not how the data is stored in the system ?",
    answer: "View Level",
    options: [
      "View Level",
      "Conceptual Level",
      "Physical Level",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following provides the ability to query information from the database and insert tuples into, delete tuples from, and modify tuples in the database?",
    answer: "DML",
    options: [
      "DDL",
      "DML",
      "Query",
      "Relational Schema"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The attribute name could be structured as an attribute consisting of first name, middle initial, and last name. This type of attribute is called",
    answer: "Composite attribute",
    options: [
      "Simple attribute",
      "Composite attribute",
      "Multivalued attribute",
      "Derived attribute"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the use of the “ORDER BY” clause in ORACLE Database ?",
    answer: "Sorting your result set using column data",
    options: [
      "Sorting your result set using column data",
      "Sorting your result set using row data",
      "Aggregation of fields",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What will be the result of “ORDER BY stu_id DESC” in the following MySQL command?  SELECT stu_id, fname, lname FROM students ORDER BY stu_id DESC;",
    answer: "Data of stu_id will be stored in descending order",
    options: [
      "Data of stu_id will be stored in ascending order",
      "Data of stu_id will be stored in descending order",
      "Data of stu_id will be stored in ascending or descending order",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which join returns all the rows from Table 2 and only those rows which match with that of Table 1 ?",
    answer: "Right Join",
    options: [
      "Inner Join",
      "Full Outer Join",
      "Right Join",
      "Left Join"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: " Given the stu_id the following set {9, 7, 6, 4, 3, 1, 2}, what will be the output on execution of the following MySQL command? SELECT stu_id FROM students ORDER BY stu_id ASC;",
    answer: "{1,2,3,4,6,7,9}",
    options: [
      "{9,7,6,4,3,1,2}",
      "{1,2,3,4,6,7,9}",
      "{2,1,3,4,6,7,9}",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "04Which among the following query retrieve rows from more than one table:  ",
    answer: "Join",
    options: [
      "End",
      "Join",
      "Start",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How many types of join are available in MYSQL ?",
    answer: "6",
    options: [
      "2",
      "3",
      "5",
      "6"
    ]
  },
];

